Right now, open you lips and begin to remove every challenge that stands against you.
You demon, you are the challenger.
We say to you right now,
come out!
Come out of my life, business and finances.
We say, come out!
Be cast out!
Begin to cast them out!
You demon!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
During the powerful mass prayer by T.B. Joshua, in the name of Jesus Christ,
the evil spirit inside this man is severely tormented as it is scorched by the fire of the Holy Ghost.
Let's hear its confession.
I am a destroyer.
The spirit of destroyer.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
[Amen.]
A Word from God can change your situation.
A Word from God can revise your situation.
The Word from God can settle the matter.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Children of God - Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Christian Attah, I'm from Kogi State.
The woman standing beside me is my lovely wife.
This is my daughter: Angel.
This is my dad: Mr. Attah.
This is my son.
This is my lovely mum: Mrs. Attah.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
I was delivered, last Sunday, when the man of God was conducting the mass prayer.
He was just praying against every evil spirit causing hindrance and setback.
We started praying that prayer along with Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Suddenly, where I was praying at the back, I found myself on the floor, screaming.
I wanted to remove my clothes!
By the time I came round, I found myself at the altar.
It all started on December 25th, 2004, when I was at school.
My friends took me out to a club where people were smoking and drinking.
They asked me if I was going to smoke.
I told them I hadn't smoked before and that my father didn't smoke or drink, so why would I start smoking?
They said I should forget about that because I was at school
and my parents were not with me – I needed to smoke.
From then, I started smoking.
After smoking, I began taking hard drugs and drinking alcohol.
One day, my friend took me to a place where gang members were.
At that place, where the gang members were gathering,
he told the members that he wanted to initiate me into their cult.
I said I didn’t want to join but they forced me, they gave me a drink and I was drunk.
Then, they beat me up seriously and gave me something to swallow.
Afterwards, they told me that no one should know that I belonged to a cult.
The next day, my friend called me and said that they wanted to go for an 'operation'.
He asked if I would follow them for the operation. I said no.
He said that it was my obligation to go and if I didn’t go, they would not see me as anything.
So, I went with them and they gave me a rifle.
We went to carry out the operation.
We got to a room with ladies inside, we took their phones, chains and all they had, then left.
You mean your colleagues called you and all of you went for what?
We went to do robbery.
- OK, robbery?
- Yes.
When we went, we abused the ladies who didn’t want to give us their money or their chains,
then they would give us their money and we would let them go.
When we got back, we would hand over the stolen goods to the senior man in the cult.
That was how my cultism started.
It affected me so badly.
At that time, I didn’t have all these tattoos on my body.
Because I was a cult member, I started getting all these tattoos.
Look at the screen of the TV.
Our brother is confessing how these evil spirits actually tormented his entire life,
to the extent that he decided to put tattoos all over his body.
He is here to tell us the exact meaning of these tattoos.
Could you explain how you came about these tattoos and their meanings?
By the tattoo on my neck,
any cultist from my former group who sees it, would know that I was a member.
Watch the screen of the TV.
We heard him explaining - he said the very tattoo on his neck is the tattoo of identification,
indicating that he belongs to a certain secret cult.
When I started drawing all these tattoos, it affected my life badly.
Sometimes, the spirit would push me to go and smoke and rob.
Especially this tattoo by my eye.
If I didn’t have money, my eyes would be red.
I would start looking for money to take drugs.
What is the meaning of the tattoo on your eyes?
These are 'tears of joy'.
OK, you call it 'tears of joy'?
Yes.
Are they really tears of joy?
To me, it doesn’t mean tears of joy but tears of sorrow.
Because I collected something by force that didn’t belong to me.
It means sorrow to me.
You mean, they are 'tears of sorrow'?
Yes.
Because you go about harassing people, and taking their things by force?
Even if my dad was talking to me, he could not look at my eyes, I would get angry.
If I was fighting with my friends, only until I saw blood, before my eyes would come down.
OK, in the course of your testimony you said you were fond of collecting things from people by force.
What do you mean by that?
Stealing people's money – I would use everything I had to collect money by force.
What were the weapons you used?
We used knives, guns and sometimes, we would use sticks as if they were guns.
Continue.
When I would come home, my younger ones would see me smoking and drinking.
That spirit influenced them and now, they are smoking even more than me.
I didn’t have any way to control them, I am the eldest in the house.
The way I behaved, they were learning from me; now, I'm delivered, I can see that those things are not good.
When I see my younger ones smoking and drinking, it's very painful because it destroys;
it doesn’t make someone move forward but backwards.
OK, can you just tell us how these evil spirits actually affected your relationship with your wife?
Sometimes, I would go out and by the time I got in, my wife would ask me
why I was going out to drink that it wasn’t good, I should consider that she was pregnant.
I would just look at her in annoyance and start beating her seriously.
There was a time I beat her to the extent that blood started flowing out of her.
You mean this demon that tormented your life made you to beat up your wife, even when she was pregnant?
Yes, I used to beat her.
Anything she said, even if it was very minor that spirit would
come into me and tell me to beat my wife and kill her.
I would press her neck, until my parents would come and rescue her from my hand.
You mean you did beat her to the extent that she was bleeding whilst she was pregnant?
Yes.
You never felt any kind of remorse?
That was then, I didn’t regret anything but now I am delivered, I don’t beat my wife any more.
OK, hold on.
Before we go to your experience after your deliverance, we have questions to ask you.
Let's come to your mum and your dad.
How did these evil spirits affect your relationship with your mum and your dad?
The evil spirit affected my mum's business so much because of the things I was doing,
they would call me to ask why I was doing all these things.
I even went somewhere to do a charm for my dad
so that anyone who wanted to help my dad should not help him.
I did that because of the day he called police and had me arrested.
This was the reason why I did it - that he would not see help from anywhere.
OK, could you just tell us what led your father to carry out that action on you?
What were you doing to your dad?
Tell us how these evil spirits affected your relationship with your dad.
I didn’t respect him; I didn’t even see him as my dad.
It was to the extent that if he wanted to slap me, I would hold him too and wanted to fight back.
It even led to misunderstanding between my mum and dad.
My dad said that he would disown me and I was not the only son he had.
But my mum didn’t agree and that was how everything happened.
OK. Now, can we come to when you were delivered?
How did you come to know about The SCOAN?
And when you came - tell us what happened to you.
It was my mum who forced me to The SCOAN!
Last Sunday, when I was in the church, the evil spirit told me that I should go and I did.
When I left, my mum was looking for me all over, then she sent my younger one to look for me.
My younger one saw me and called me back inside; when I came back,
the spirit was pushing me to go out and smoke, asking me why I was staying in the church.
When I came back, my mum was angry with me and asked me why I went out.
I didn’t even answer her.
During the mass prayer, I didn’t know what came over me.
There was something like fire that was burning inside me, so I wanted to take off my clothes!
I wanted to run away but I felt chained down; the Spirit of God did not allow me to go out.
Eventually, I fell down and saw myself at the altar.
OK, can you tell us - ever since you have been delivered,
what are the changes you have noticed in your life and in relations with your family?
Now, I love my wife; we are on good terms.
I no longer go out with friends, I even broke my SIM, so those bad friends can't call me again.
I don't go out.
When my mum is talking to me now, I always listen to her.
This tattoo on my arm, I used it to deceive ladies.
Sometimes, I would take a lady out, telling her that I wanted to help her.
I would take her to a hotel room and she would think it was only me who wanted to sleep with her
but when we got to the hotel room, we would drug her
and she would not know what was happening, a group of us would abuse her.
This tattoo is the head of an eagle.
OK, the head of an eagle?
Since I am delivered, I no longer smoke.
The day I was delivered, I had a dream.
I saw my friends in a place where they were smoking.
They called me to join them to smoke and I went.
I took a drag of a cigarette and took a second one;
on the third drag, I was about to take, something started coming out of my nose.
Then, a voice told me to look at my left.
When I looked at my left, I saw worldly people, then I looked at my right
I saw Prophet T.B. Joshua holding my hand.
Holding my hand, Prophet T.B. Joshua took me to a room where people were singing praises.
Someone was sat on a throne and there was light.
I asked the man of God if I could see the person sitting on the throne.
He asked if I had eyes to see and if God gave me eyes to see the person, would I be able to stand?
I said that I wanted to see the person.
Next, I heard a loud voice from the throne.
He said, "Christian, do you know the meaning of Christian?"
I said no. He said, Christian is Christ-like and that I needed to follow the way of Christ.
That is the meaning of Christian.
Then, I woke up from the dream.
Wow, shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God.
This is a clear proof that indeed the deliverance the brother has received here,
at The SCOAN, the arena of liberty, is genuine.
Of course, the dream has gone as far as telling him the meaning of being a Christian.
This means a Christ-like person.
In other words he should make the Word of God the standard for his life
and follow Jesus Christ for the rest of his life.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully.
Now, as you are completely delivered - can you tell us how you relate with your mum, dad and wife?
We are all happy now and things I didn’t do for my mum before, I am doing now.
Now, we are at peace and between me and my wife there is peace.
Let's clap for Jesus Christ for that.
Madam, welcome in Jesus' name.
We believe this is a day of your joy.
Could you just tell us your name and your own side of the story?
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Rita Attah, I'm from Kogi State.
People of God - my testimony goes like this:
when I met my husband, he was smoking, drinking, womanising, always going to clubs.
I didn't know that my husband was acting like that after having taken different drugs.
Each time I asked him about this going out he would start beating me up.
He would lay his hand on me even while I was pregnant.
The reason for which I am here is to testify that my husband does not do those things any more.
The smoking, drinking, going out to clubs, womanising - my husband does not do those things any more.
My husband stays at home, ministers the Anointing Water, reads the Bible and prays - he gathers our family...
Mrs Rita Attah
Deliverance Testimony
To God be the glory.
We thank God Almighty for your life.
Let's hear from the father of your husband.
People of God - Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Samson Attah, I'm from Kogi State.
Today is a great day for me.
I've suffered a lot because of my first son.
My son was born in 1985.
My son was well till the age of eleven years.
When I moved to Lagos, I started to notice something about my son.
When I called him, he wouldn't answer my call.
There was no respect.
I told my wife that I noticed something about our son - Christian.
He would not even like to attend the morning devotion.
The rest of children would attend the morning devotion.
Whenever I called him to attend morning devotion, he wouldn't like to answer me.
I started to notice some things.
He changed entirely at the age of 15, after finishing secondary school.
I told him I didn't like his friends, that he should go away from them, and their way of living was bad.
Then the battle between me and my son began.
When I advised him like that, he would insult me.
When he began to insult me, the younger son would attack him.
One day, when he was insulting me, I slapped him and he held my hand and wanted to beat me.
The junior one insulted him and he was holding him.
Because of that he made a comment that he would call a gang, and I would not see that boy again,
and the following day I would see him dead on the street.
I called my wife and I said that this boy had gone far towards "something".
One day I came while he was sleeping...
The tattoo on the arm was his first one.
When I saw the tattoo, I asked my son what the meaning of it was.
He started telling me that this didn't concern me, and I should not ask him.
One day, he gathered a group of people - cult members on the street.
They were fighting with broken bottles and jumping over the fence.
Then, my junior son came - he saw that Christian and his group wanted to kill someone.
I was laying on my bed.
When I got up, I looked through the window and I saw him and people that were coming.
I fainted.
I did not know what was happening for more than one hour.
I saw those things: the broken bottles, someone being injured - so I fainted.
Then I told my wife that I would report this boy to the police, so they would arrest him.
Since he wanted to kill the junior son, one day we might not see our son any more.
My wife said that we should wait and not go to the police.
I said OK.
After that he started again.
I called him - he refused to come.
And now the worst thing happened - he polluted the minds of the junior ones.
They used to come to the morning devotion before - he told them many things.
Those who were not smoking before started to smoke.
Those that had not been stealing before - he told them how to make money faster than me, as a father, did.
When I called them, they did not listen to me any more.
Everything was tough between me and him.
One day, I told him that I would disown him.
He started fighting me.
Then I met with my second son and my wife.
The three of us tried to keep and beat him - we couldn't do that.
Then I escaped because he was focused on me.
Whatever I did or said, it was like fire for him.
He didn't want to see me at all.
I told my wife...
One day he gathered some people to kill me because I was the one giving him a tough time.
I was the one troubling him - he wanted to kill me.
When this information came to me, I escaped because this boy with other people was ready to kill me.
It was last year - January 11th - I made up my mind to quit my house.
That day I run away to Ghana.
I went to my friend and stayed there to save my life.
I told my wife that I would not come back until this boy was delivered.
Otherwise he would take my life.
When I went to Ghana, I asked my friend - we began to pray.
This is my first son - I have suffered a lot; all my businesses collapsed.
There was no one to take care of my business.
There was no money for me anymore.
We continued to pray.
I was praying for my first son to be delivered; Christian to be delivered -
that was my prayer point number one.
I, my friend and his wife were praying together three weeks ago.
Then our Prophet appeared to me in the dream.
That was three weeks ago.
Prophet said, "Son, you should not worry. The answer to your prayer has come. The whole thing is settled."
Immediately I heard that voice, I woke up.
In the morning I called my wife.
I said that I had been praying and that I saw Prophet T.B. Joshua in my dream.
He said that the case of my son Christian was settled and that I should take all of them to the church.
Since the Prophet said the case was settled, I believed it.
Last Sunday, my wife brought all of them here.
I started with Emmanuel TV
because Emmanuel TV is my friend, mother, father, wife, it is my everything.
I sleep and wake up with Emmanuel TV.
Last Sunday in the morning I was watching Emmanuel TV.
I was watching the prayer, the testimonies...
When the man of God appeared and prophesied to people, I asked God, "Please, locate my son".
As I was watching, I saw some people coming out.
One lady came out, then another lady came out.
I continued to pray.
I opened my eyes and I saw my son in the front of the altar.
That is not enough for Jesus Christ!
Put your hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God.
When they brought him out, he was saying, "I destroy, I destroy".
I started to see all these things.
I said, "God - You are wonderful".
As he entered the arena of liberty, all the problems were settled.
That is how I gave thanks to my God.
When I was in Lagos, my son didn't talk to me, he didn't call me, he didn't want to see me.
After I went to Ghana, he didn't call me even once, he didn't think about me.
On Tuesday morning...
You mean after his deliverance?
After his deliverance on Sunday.
On Monday...
On Tuesday in the morning there was I call.
Since my son was not calling me, I didn't know his number.
I didn't even think about my son.
The only call I was expecting from Nigeria was from my wife.
I used to talk with my wife every day.
So the call came in.
He said, "Good morning, daddy".
I asked, "Who is this?"
I asked, "Is it Israel?"
He said, "No. I'm Christian - your first son".
I answered, "Mr. Attah speaking. Is it a mistake?"
Mr Samson Attah & Family
Deliverance Testimony
I said, "No. It might be a wrong number. This is Mr. Attah talking. Who are you?"
He said, "I'm Christian - your first son. It is not a mistake.
I collected your number from my mum on Monday."
I said, "You!?"
He said, "Yes."
I said, "Yes, my prayer has been answered because I saw you."
Mr Samson Attah & Family
Deliverance Testimony
God has answered my prayer.
Because God spoke to me in the dream through Prophet T.B. Joshua saying that the case was settled,
I knew that the case was settled.
My son said, "Dad, I want you to come to Nigeria. I want to sit down and discuss with you."
I asked, "Should I come?"
I was not sure because maybe he had gathered some gang to attack me - so I had to call my wife.
I called my wife.
I told my wife that I had a call from Christian.
He said that I should come to Lagos, Nigeria.
I asked my wife if it was indeed him with her.
She said, "He asked me for your number and I gave it to him."
I asked, "Have you confirmed that nothing would happen to me if I returned?"
She said, "Yes, you should come - it is confirmed."
I came back in the night.
Since all these things started, he never hugged me.
That day I came - Wednesday - when I reached the house, he was the first person than run and hugged me.
Mr Samson Attah & Family
Deliverance Testimony
When he hugged me, I looked at him and started shedding tears.
Yesterday he came to me.
He didn't discuss anything with me before.
When he came to me, he said, "Dad, if you have any dirty clothes for me to wash and iron for you...
On Sunday we will go to church."
I said, "I ironed all my clothes before coming back from Ghana. So, there is no problem".
I said to him that if he wanted us to go to the church, I was ready to go.
He said, "OK".
These things have not been seen before.
It used to be like cat and rat, lion in the house.
Everything was disorganized.
This boy used to beat his pregnant wife.
That was before he was delivered?
That was before he was delivered.
Now, when his wife carries water to the bathroom, they go together, bathing together...
It is wonderful.
I am happy today.
To God be the glory.
Once again, let's put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God.
Yes sir, we will get back to you to hear your words of advice, especially to parents,
but before, we want to hear from the mum.
God is wonderful.
Especially, the God of T.B. Joshua is a wonderful God.
My name is Mrs Attah.
The boy beside me is my first son and his wife.
This is my loving husband.
Because of my son, our love divided but I am thanking God today.
My testimony goes like this.
When I married my husband, his grandfather was the one who married us.
His grandfather was a native doctor.
When I was pregnant, I gave birth to a baby boy who is this Christian Attah.
Seven days after his birth, we gave him the name of the grandfather
which was the first name before we gave him Christian.
We gave him the name Abata.
When my son grew to about five years old, ten, eleven and fourteen, he started behaving waywardly.
When he went out, sometimes three days would pass before he came home.
They used to call me and say that my son was fighting somewhere.
When I got there, I would see my son with a glass bottle or a knife fighting.
I would hold Christian and ask him what his problem was.
When we finished secondary school, we asked Christian what he wanted to do.
He replied that he wanted to be a solider.
I said he should join but I did not know that the army he joined
was doing armed robbery and putting tattoos on his body.
When Prophet T.B. Joshua began the mass prayer, God Almighty arrested my son.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Since your son has been delivered, what are the changes you have seen in his life?
Since that Sunday when my son was delivered, I have been happy.
What my son couldn’t ask me for before, he now asks me.
First of all, he asked me for his dad's phone number.
Since then, my son's character has changed.
He doesn’t go out anymore.
Sometimes, he calls his junior ones to sit down with them and talk to them.
This is what my son would never do before.
Shall we clap for wonderful Jesus Christ!
Yes, we thank God Almighty for what He has done in your life, in the life of your son and also the entire family.
Now, what word of advice do you have for parents and everyone?
I pray that God will answer those who have the same problem I once had,
in the same way He answered me, in Jesus' name.
Amen. Let's clap for wonderful Jesus Christ.
Now, let's hear the word of advice from Christian.
My word of advice goes like this.
In Romans 12:1 it says, "I beseech you therefore, brethren…
Let's clap for Jesus Christ for that.
To God be the glory.
You can see the whole church is happy with you.
I believe that is how the Kingdom of Heaven is rejoicing because of your deliverance.
In Romans 12:1 it says, "I beseech you therefore, brethren, by the mercy of God,
that we may present our bodies holy and acceptable unto God."
So, what I want to tell the youth is to present themselves in a way that is acceptable to God.
The worldly things I was into before don’t make sense.
Now, I thank God that He delivered me and the same God that delivered me will deliver you too.
The same Christian that was carrying cutlass, guns and knife is now carrying the Holy Bible.
I thank God.
Let's put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
To God be the glory.
Let's hear finally from your dad - a word of advice.
The word of my advice is that as parents we should monitor our children - the way they behave.
I want you to know that this battle for our children is not physical.
I have "used" police, my strength, the strength of my wife, my junior son, and everybody -
but prayer is the answer!
If anything affects your children, go into prayer.
That is my advice to all parents.
Let's put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Indeed, prayer is the master key to loose and to bind.
We thank God Almighty for what He has accomplished first and foremost
in the life of your son Christian and the entire family.
I also want you to know that as much as your son is delivered through the Word of God,
we believe he has started the journey of salvation by making the Word of God
the standard for his life and of course for the entire family.
Always have it at the back of your mind that better is not good enough - the best is always yet to come.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for the miracle-working God!
Mr Christian Attah & Family
Deliverance Testimony
RV: Mel Flowers 23/02/2019